export const Feedbacks = [
    {
      prompt: "What is the primary source of energy for most power grids around the world?",
      generalFeedback: "While the mix of energy sources varies by region, fossil fuels remain the dominant source for electricity generation globally, though renewable sources are on the rise."
    },
    {
      prompt: "How does electricity typically travel from power plants to consumers?",
      generalFeedback: "Electricity is generated at power plants and then transmitted over long distances via high-voltage transmission lines. It's then distributed to consumers through lower-voltage distribution networks."
    },
    {
      prompt: "Why is energy efficiency important in homes and businesses?",
      generalFeedback: "Energy efficiency is crucial for reducing energy consumption, lowering energy bills, and minimizing the environmental footprint by decreasing greenhouse gas emissions."
    },
    {
      prompt: "What is the primary goal of demand management in energy usage?",
      generalFeedback: "Demand management aims to ensure energy is used more efficiently, balancing the supply with the fluctuating demand to maintain grid stability and reduce costs."
    },
    {
      prompt: "Which of the following is a common method used in demand management to encourage lower energy use during peak hours?",
      generalFeedback: "Lowering rates or providing incentives for reduced energy use during peak hours helps smooth out energy demand, benefiting both the grid and consumer."
    },
    {
      prompt: "Benefits to the consumer from demand management include:",
      generalFeedback: "Participating in demand management programs can lead to significant savings on electricity bills for consumers by incentivizing energy use during off-peak hours."
    },
    {
      prompt: "How does implementing demand management strategies benefit the environment?",
      generalFeedback: "Implementing demand management strategies plays a crucial role in environmental conservation by reducing the reliance on non-renewable energy sources and minimizing carbon emissions."
    },
    {
      prompt: "What can be a direct benefit of participating in a demand management program for consumers?",
      generalFeedback: "Participation in demand management programs often results in direct benefits for consumers, such as savings on electricity bills, by encouraging energy use during less expensive, off-peak hours."
    },
    {
      prompt: "Why is load shifting important in demand management?",
      generalFeedback: "Load shifting is a critical component of demand management, aimed at moving energy use from peak to off-peak hours. This helps balance the power grid, reduces the need for additional power plants, and can lead to cost savings for consumers and utility providers alike."
    },
    {
      prompt: "Which of the following electric loads can be effectively managed as part of a demand management program?",
      generalFeedback: "Demand management programs focus on adjusting the usage of flexible and non-critical electric loads to optimize energy consumption. Residential air conditioning units, for example, can be adjusted without compromising safety or critical operations, making them ideal for inclusion in these programs."
    },
  ];
  